A Guide to the Papers of the Prince Edward County Free School 1963-1967
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- Student Records
  - Standardized Test (Box 63-106)
    Gates reading survey, the Stanford Achievement, The Wechsler Intelligence Scale, The Chuazz nonverbal standardized (Student from Michigan State) Administrated Stanford and Metropolitan Test).Restrictions apply
    - Student Transcripts
  - Transcripts (Box 63-106)
    Student enrolled in the Prince Edward County Free School from 1963-1964. Restrictions Apply
- Photographs (Box 107)
  Documents printed by the Prince Edward County Free School Association. There are also a number of other items which were collected by the Free School Administrators.
- Printed (Box 107-109)
  - Yearbooks, The Eagle (Box 107)
  - Newsletters, The Moton Eagle, The Branch Informer (2) (Box 107)
  - Programs and Bulletins
    - Program: Memorial Service John F. Kennedy (Box-folder 108:1)
    - Program: Robert Kennedy (Box-folder 108:2)
    - Branch # 1 1963 (Box-folder 108:3)
    - Program: The Library Club (Box-folder 108:4)
    - Programs: 1963-1964 (Box-folder 108:5)
    - Program: Commencement Robert R. Moton 1964 (Box-folder 108:6)
    - Program: Testimonial Neel v. Sullivan (Box-folder 108:7)
  - News Clippings (Box 108)
  - Office Supplies (Box 109)